Bridge pose is a classic finishing pose that can be done in prenatal yoga.
As long as it's still comfortable for you to be lying on your back.
Are you comfortable?
I do have a blanket underneath her head for just a little bit of support on her neck.
Alright, bridge pose.
You want to bring your feet about hip width apart, heels slightly closer to the hips than you normally would, arms dropped down to your sides, palms on the earth.
Important to work with your breath in this pose.
Take a nice deep inhale.
As you exhale, press into the feet, lift the hips up slightly.
Now you don't want to take it to the full limit, perfect.
Now press in the hips up to the sky.
Nice gentle strengthening of the spine, helps relieve some tension.
Keep looking straight up.
Whenever you have any constriction on the neck, not looking side to side.
Keep looking straight up to the sky, pressing your arms down into the mat.
If it's comfortable for you, if it's part of your practice, you can bring the arms underneath you into moodrem.
I think she prefers to bring it into moodrem.
Perfect.
Clasp the fingers together, press the arms into the mat.
You also have to come a little bit higher onto those shoulders, lovely.
One more nice breath holding the pose.
Long complete exhale.
Release the hands out to your sides, press up onto your tippy toes, take a nice deep inhale, exhale very slowly, very gently, lowering down one vertebrae at a time.
Always going in and out of bridge as slow as you possibly can.
Perfect.
Whenever you're done, you can release the heels back towards the earth.
Beautiful.